[
  {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "In society, different kinds of institutions are created to meet the needs of the people, such as _______, ________, ________, and more.",
      "answer": ["schools", "hospitals", "government offices"]
  },
  {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "_______ plays a key role in ensuring that a school fulfills its mission of providing quality education.",
      "answer": "Management"
  },
  {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "To manage an institution means to plan, organize, _______, _______, and control resources.",
      "answer": ["direct", "delegate"]
  },
  {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "_______ refers to the people who are in charge of an organization, such as principals and department heads.",
      "answer": "Management as a noun"
  },
  {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "When we talk about management as a process, it includes key functions like _______, _______, _______, _______, and controlling.",
      "answer": ["planning", "organizing", "staffing", "delegating"]
  },
  {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "_______ involves learning theories, concepts, principles, and procedures that help people become good managers.",
      "answer": "Management as a discipline"
  },
  {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "In education management, one of the key aspects is to ensure that the resources, like _______, _______, _______, and ________, are effectively organized.",
      "answer": ["teachers", "classrooms", "textbooks", "technology"]
  },
  {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "_______ refers to overseeing and guiding the various activities of an educational institution to ensure it runs smoothly and achieves its goals.",
      "answer": "Management of education"
  },
  {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "The goal of education management is to effectively and efficiently accomplish the functions of the institution, such as _______, _______, _______, and ________.",
      "answer": ["teaching", "learning", "research", "extension work"]
  },
  {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "________ refers to education that goes beyond the classroom, such as community outreach and connecting with local businesses.",
      "answer": "Extension work"
  }
]
